ELIJAH BUSICK

FULL-STACK JAVA DEVELOPER

LINKEDIN

GITHUB

PERSONAL PORTFOLIO



ABOUT ME

Recent graduate of Cognixia's JUMP program, a hyper-intense technical training program that gives top STEM talent from across the U.S. the equivalent of 12-18 months of industry experience. I have up skilled my technical abilities and evolved my digital mindset to successfully adapt and utilize technology in an efficient manner so I can JUMP start my career via deployment with Collabera clients.

EDUCATION

ACHIEVEMENTS

TOP SKILLS

Western Carolina University

Bachelor of Marketing and Sales

2018-2020

UNC of Charlotte

Full-Stack Web Developer Certification

- Responsive Web Design
- Future Business Leaders of America
- Proficient in writing Italian

- Java
- HTML
- SQL
- CSS
- React
- JavaScript
- Nodejs

EXPERIENCE

Cognixia

Nov 2022 - Present

Full-Stack Java Developer

- Developed a Full suite Spring Boot REST API, implementing Spring Security, Hibernate, JPA, and Mockito Test Suite
- Database Proficiency in RDBMS MySQL as well as NoSQL with MongoDB
- Developed responsive SPA Front End Interface using ReactJS

Best Buy

Oct 2021 - Jun 2022

Sales Associate

- Assisted customers determining technical issues with previous bought products
- · Process client's transactions

PROJECTS

My Doctor

Social Media App

JavaScript, CSS, Bootstrap, MySQL, Handlebars, NodeJS.

My Doctor is an easy to use social media like application for doctors to answer patient questions on a variety of topics concerning health of patients.

EMS Project GitHub

Employee Management System

Java

EMS is a console Java project that adds, removes, update and list employee